mediacpm.com 2013-06-03

# Privacy

**Privacy Policy** Last Updated: July 5, 2011 

Company/Site: Mediacpm.com 

Site URL: http://www.Mediacpm.com.com 

Introduction 

Mediacpm.com respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our website only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at Mediacpm.com. 

**Information Collection**

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs and to customize our service to make your experience easier. 

Mediacpm.com collects the following information about primary visitors: Your Name, Company Name, Address, Telephone Number, E-mail address, website URL, PayPal or alertPay E-mail addresses, Financial Institution and corresponding information. 

We may also collect certain types of personally identifiable information which our users divulge about other people, such as referrals, gift purchases or other situations. We automatically collect electronic information such as IP address, browser type, referrer URL and other technical data. 

Mediacpm.com collects this information through methods such as registration forms, email communications, etc. The information is collected voluntarily. This information is needed to provide you with the requested services and will not be shared, sold or viewed by anyone other than Mediacpm.com employees. 

We verify the accuracy of the gathered information by validating via email addresses. 

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our website. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies can also help us provide information which is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, however some parts of our website may not work properly if you do so. 

Please note that your personally identifiable information will be stored and processed on our dedicated servers in USA and/or Canada. The North American laws on holding personal data may differ from the European laws but we will hold and transmit your information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. 

As a matter of policy, we never sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. 

**Information Usage**

We use information in the files we maintain about you, and the other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the website to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems and/or resolve disputes. Mediacpm.com maintains the accuracy of information by cross-checking its own databases and validating users emails. 

**If you are an Advertiser or Agency**

Mediacpm.com may disclose your contact information to potential Publishers on whose websites you are willing or have already placed advertisements. 

**If you are a Publisher**

Mediacpm.com may share information about your website, including but not limited to: page impressions, website traffic, inventory rates, etc. with Advertisers, Agencies, and other media partners. We will not share your personal identifiable information with third-party without your prior written or electronic consent. 

You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our website's content, layout, and services. These uses improve our website and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

The information collected by Mediacpm.com will be used for strictly internal purposes only. Users who provide the information will receive email announcements or advertisements pertaining only to our services. Registered users may receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, new features, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. 

The information we collect will not be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history. We will not supplement information collected at our website with data from other sources such as credit history to authorize purchases. 

We may share data with the following third parties: PayPal, AlertPay, or other third party online payment processors/services that are necessary to carry out a transaction. These third parties will use the information only for a transaction between you and Mediacpm.com. We have NO access to any information collected by these Online Payment Services Providers. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads as a background. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here 

Sometimes, we may offer links to other websites. Please note: When you click on links to other websites, we encourage you to read their Privacy Policies. Their standards may differ from ours. 

**Children**

Mediacpm.com does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child to divulge personal information. If you are not at least 18 years of age, please do not open an account and/or use our website's services. 

**Control of Your Password**

You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password. Therefore, we do not recommend that you disclose your Mediacpm.com password or login information to any third parties.  
If you choose to share this information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password and therefore should review each third party's Privacy Policy.   
If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

**Data Storage and Security** Mediacpm.com protects user information with the following security measures: security protocols, secure servers, firewalls, SSL encryption and other latest technology and procedures used to protect consumer privacy. 

**Problem Resolution**

If problems arise, users may contact Mediacpm.com via Contact Us form. We are committed to resolving disputes within a reasonable time frame. 

**Notice of Changes**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and our needs to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. You have the opportunity to notify Mediacpm.com if you do not agree to such changes. 

If you have any questions, comments, criticisms, or complaints about Mediacpm.com's Privacy Policy, please feel free to Contact Us . Customer Service representatives are available to assist you Monday through Friday from 9:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. EDT. 

Please read our Terms and Conditions carefully before using this website. 

**Copyright © 2012 Mediacpm.com | All rights reserved. | Registered[Jersey CI Company](https://www.jerseyfsc.org/registry/documentsearch/NameDetail.aspx?id=286243) **
